Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Gay USA, 154212
  - 1993 Vol. XI, 246293
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 17 [Air date: 4/22/1993], April 1993; ID: 231.0138; 154371 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0138)
      8. "Naming Names": Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a NY Times article regarding the percentage of people who identify as homosexual.
      9. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Marjorie Hill, NYC Mayor Dinkins' Liaison to the gay and lesbian community, regarding political events that affect the LGBT community.
      10. Clip of music video for "I Melt with You" by Modern English.
      11. Clip of two men kissing with message "Get Used to It".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 18 [Air date: 4/29/1993], April 1993; ID: 231.0139; 154372 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0139)
      1. Footage from the March on Washington of the candlelight vigil honoring gay and lesbian Holocaust victims.
      2. Footage from the March on Washington of the HRCF black tie dinner. Includes footage of Ted Kennedy, Democratic Senator from Massachusetts, and Dorothy Hodges, mother of hate crime victim Allen Schindler.
      3. Footage from the March on Washington of the Victory Fund brunch that honored lesbian and gay appointed officials. Includes footage of [James Carville], Clinton Campaign Strategist, and [Tim Mains], Mayoral Candidate for Rochester, NY.
      4. Footage from the March on Washington of "The Wedding; Interfaith Ceremony of Commitment".
      5. Footage from the March on Washington of Ken McPherson discussing the Harvey Milk Memorial design unveiling.
      6. Footage from the March on Washington "Hands Around the Capitol" event by ACTUP. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Anna Lee, activist, regarding AIDS.
      7. Footage from the March on Washington of the National Gathering of Lesbian and Gay Latinos. Includes Andy Humm interviewing [Laura] Esquivel, Co-Founder of LLEGO (Latino/a Lesbian & Gay Organization).
      8. Footage from the March on Washington of the National Meeting of Asian/Pacific [Lesbian] Network. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Doreena Wong, Organizer of NMAPLN.
      9. Footage from the March on Washington of the benefit reception for the Gay Games. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Dave Kopay, out-[gay] NFL football player.
      10. Footage from the March on Washington of Youth Empowerment Speakout. Includes interview with Karina Luboff, Coordinator of Youth Empowerment Speakout.
      11. Footage from the March on Washington of the Veteran Taps Ceremony.
      12. Footage from the March on Washington of the Gay & Lesbian Parents Coalition International (GLPCI). Includes Andy Humm interviewing [Suzanne Putman], Vice President of GLPCI, and [John Sheets], President of GLPCI.
      13. Footage from the March on Washington of the Dyke March sponsored by the Lesbian Avengers. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing [Theressa Stores], Boston marcher; [Catherine Wendricks], Organizer of Venus Rising
      14. Footage from the March on Washington of "Spring to Life" event. Includes interview with [Rob Eichberg].
      15. Footage from the March on Washington of the actual march. Includes Andy Humm interviewing members of the Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), and Jill Harris, NY School Board Candidate for District 15.
      16. Footage from the March on Washington of the Names Project Quilt, various speakers, and performance by Melissa Etheridge.
      17. Interview: Dick Dadey, of the Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses the upcoming NY School Board elections.
      18. "Naming Names": Lisa Graziano, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent segment of the ABC news magazine show Primetime regarding gays and lesbians in the military. Includes footage of Primetime segment.
      COMMERCIAL: Manatus Restaurant
      19. "Lavender Health": Ellen Zaltzberg, of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Marjorie Hill, Vice President of the NYC Health and Hospitals Corporation, regarding her work and achievements. Includes footage of [Florynce Kennedy], [activist]; Dr. Billy Jones, President of the NYC Health and Hospitals Corporation; and Sandra Lowe.
      20. Footage from the March on Washington of Andy Humm and Lee Sharmat with several attendees.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 19 [Air date: 5/6/1993], May 1993; ID: 231.0140A; 154373 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0140A)
      2. Lee Sharmat interviews Sergeant Jose Zuniga, recipient of the "Soldier of the Year Award".
      3. Footage of reception for Robert A. Schanke. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Robert A. Schanke, author, regarding his book "Shattered Applause: The Eva Le Gallienne Story". Also includes Lee Sharmat interviewing [Jonathan Katz], author, regarding his book "Gay American History".
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Charlie Murphy, Composer, and Jami Sieber, Electric Cellist/Singer, regarding their band "Rumors of the Big Wave". Includes performance footage from the March on Washington.
      5. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Cathy Woolard, Acting Public Policy Director for HRCF, who discusses the hearings regarding gays in the military.
      6. "Naming Names": Ellen Carton, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses censorship by CBS of an already-filmed clip of the show "Picket Fences".
      7. Interview: Michelangelo Signorile, author, discusses his book "Queer in America: Sex, the Media, and the Closets of Power".
      8. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Victoria C. Metaxas, Assistant Corporation Counsel for the NYC Law Department, and Irwin B. Kroot, Director of [Citywide Computer Training Program], regarding their organization "Coalition of Lesbian and Gay City Employees" in NYC.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 20 [Air date: 5/13/1993], May 1993; ID: 231.0141; 154374 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0141)
      2. Footage of PrideFest Philadelphia 1993. Includes interview with [Malcolm Lazin], Co-Chair of PrideFest, and Beth Medoway, of Artists for AIDS.
      3. [Footage from PrideFest Philadelphia 1993 of] Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) political seminar, which includes interview with Tim McFeeley, Executive Director of HRCF; and Jeffrey Schmalz, NY Times reporter.
      4. [Footage from PrideFest Philadelphia 1993 of] White Heat party fundraiser for AIDS Information Network
      5. Interview: Catherine Sull, Chair of Board for CBST [Congregation Beit Simchat Torah], the gay and lesbian synagogue, and Arthur Strickler, Past Chair for CBST, discuss the exclusion of their group from the Salute to Israel Day Parade.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Martin Duberman, historian/author, regarding his book "Stonewall".
      7. "Naming Names": Chiqui Cartagena, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent homophobic article in the New Yorker magazine.
      8. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Mark Milano, AIDS activist, regarding sex clubs.
      9. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Terry Beswick, AIDS Research Policy Analyst for HRCF, regarding funding for AIDS research.
      10. Interview: Professor Arthur Leonard, Legal Scholar/Author, discusses the gay marriage case in Hawaii.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 21 [Air date: 5/20/1993], May 1993; ID: 231.0142; 154375 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0142)
      2. Interview: Dennis deLeon, NYC Human Rights Commissioner, discusses the recent public revelation of his HIV-positive status.
      3. Lou Maletta interviews David Mixner, [activist], regarding President Bill Clinton's actions and promises to the gay community.
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Terry Schleder, President of Boycott Colorado Inc., and Frank Whitworth, Ground Zero [News] Spokesman, regarding the boycott of Colorado and the gay rights movement.
      5. GCN Sports: Bill Baumer, Founder of "Out the Window" comedy troupe, interviews Gutter George, President of the Village Bowling League, regarding his bowling teams.
      6. Elizabeth McNamara, Co-Chair of Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund's Board of Directors, encourages viewers to attend the organization's 20th anniversary gala.
      7. Lou Maletta interviews [Rod Jackson and Bob Paris], of the Be True to Yourself Foundation, regarding the functions of their organization.
      8. "Naming Names": Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses an exhibit featuring lesbian softball players at the NYC Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA) Yankee Stadium station.
      9. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Mark Milano, Coordinator of Experimental Treatment Information for the New York State AIDS Institute, regarding clinical trials of AIDS drugs.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 22 [Air date: 5/27/1993], May 1993; ID: 231.0143; 154376 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0143)
      1. Lee Sharmat discusses recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Lee Sharmat interviews [Andy Velez], of ACTUP, regarding the 9th annual AIDS conference in Berlin.
      3. Lee Sharmat interviews Amber Hollibaugh, of Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), regarding the 9th annual AIDS conference in Berlin.
      4. Andy Humm discusses "Don't Ask, Don't Tell".
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Kevin Gardner, Director of the AESOP Resource Center, and Pavel Masalsky, of the Russian Names Fund, regarding AIDS in Russia.
      6. Danny Dromm, Co-Chair of the Queens Lesbian and Gay Pride Committee, encourages viewers to attend the first ever lesbian and gay pride parade and block party.
      7. Lee Sharmat interviews Jill Harris, newly elected NYC School Board member, regarding her election win.
      8. "Naming Names": Tom Trela, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent Entertainment Weekly article.
      9. "Lavender Health": Gregory Broyles, Director of the [Men of Color AIDS Prevention (MOCA)], interviews Ronald Johnson, Citywide Coordinator for AIDS Policy for the Office of the Mayor, regarding AIDS-related issues. Also includes interview with Chris Babick, Executive Director of the PWA (People With AIDS) Coalition, regarding his organization's functions.
      10. Footage of Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund [benefit]. Includes footage of Kate Clinton, comedienne / M.C. Liberty Awards; Lou Maletta interviewing Betty Buckley, singer and actress; Hon. David Dinkins, Mayor of NYC; Ron Johnson, NYC's First AIDS Czar; and Andrea Marcovicci, entertainer.
      11. Cee Brown, of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, discusses an upcoming benefit dinner. Includes footage of "Sacred Lives, Civil Truths" by [Catherine Saalfield and Cyrille Phipps].
      12. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Tom Swift, National Canvas Manager of Speak Out for HRCF, regarding the Speak Out program.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 23 [Air date: 6/3/1993], June 1993; ID: 231.0144; 154377 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0144)
      1. Andy Humm and Lee Sharmat discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community. Includes NY1 footage Reverend Luis Barrios, priest, who discusses his [possibly] racially-motivated ousting for performing gay and lesbian unions.
      2. Interview: April Martin, Ph.D., author, discusses her book "Lesbian and Gay Parenting Handbook".
      3. GCN Sports: Bill Baumer, Founder of "Out the Window" comedy troupe, interviews Gutter George, President of the Village Bowling League, regarding his personal life.
      4. Footage of the Gay and Lesbian World Travel Expo. Includes footage of Lou Maletta interviewing Christopher K., of Cardona Limousine; Barry R. Gruber, General Manager of Rainbow Mountain Resort; Steve Jackson, of Pride Tours [with] Kennedy Travel; and Edwin M. Andino, of Harrington Travel.
      5. [Unnamed] discusses Parker Tyler, film critic and author of "Screening the Sexes: Homosexuality in the Movies", and the 1993 Lesbian and Gay Film Festival.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews [Franklin Fry] and Sue Doster, Co-Chairs of Heritage of Pride, regarding upcoming Pride events. Includes footage of June 1991 Gay Pride Parade.
      7. Alfonso Ramirez, of the Metropolitan Tennis Group NYC, promotes the upcoming Tournament of Pride "Liberty Open".
      8. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Richard Burns, Executive Director of the Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center, regarding the Center.
      9. Andy Humm discusses the recent death of Ermanno Stingo, activist.
      10. "Naming Names": Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent episode of Oprah Winfrey that focused on a husband and wife who were "cured" of their homosexuality before they met.
      11. [Unnamed] discusses the film "Silverlake Life: The View from Here". Includes film footage.
      12. In England, Andy Humm interviews Reverend Bernard Lynch, AIDS Educator in London; James Pettigrew, of London PWA; and Andrew Henderson, of London Lighthouse for PWA's. Includes footage of candlelight memorial, which includes Simon Callow, actor / Trafalgar Sq. AIDS Memorial; and Andy Humm interviewing a gay youth worker and other attendees.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 24 [Air date: 6/10/1993], June 1993; ID: 231.0145; 154378 (Box 10, Media ID: 231.0145)
      Physical Requirements and Technical Requirements
      2. Lee Sharmat interviews Torie Osborn, Executive Director of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, regarding her new position as Executive Director.
      COMMERCIAL: Elizabeth Taylor for AmFAR, "Don't make it five thousand and one"
      3. Footage of Andy Humm and Lee Humm at the first annual Queens Gay and Lesbian Pride Parade.
      4. Footage of Broadway Cares/Equity Fights AIDS benefit. Includes Lou Maletta interviewing [Rodger McFarlane], Executive Director of Broadway Cares/Equity Fights AIDS, regarding the benefit. Also includes speech by Mary Fisher, a person living with AIDS.
      COMMERCIAL: Affirmative Lifestyles
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Edna Benitez and Tony Meola, Race Directors of the 12th annual Front Runners Lesbian and Gay Pride Run, regarding the upcoming run.
      6. Footage of the Hetrick-Martin Emery Awards. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Marjorie Hill, Vice President of the NYC Health and Hospitals Corporation; various youth from the Hetrick-Martin Institute; and Essex Hemphill, Emery S. Hetrick Award recipient.
      7. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Richard Burns, Executive Director of the Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center, regarding the Center.
      8. Interview: Jose Badue, of the Gay and Lesbian Association of Cuban Exiles, discusses the film "Beyond Outcasts" by David Hernandez and Ivan Arocha, as well as HIV/AIDS quarantines in Haiti and Cuba. Includes film footage.
      9. Lou Maletta interviews Peter Friedman, Producer, regarding his film "Silverlake Life: The View from Here". Includes film footage.
      COMMERCIAL: Lesbian and Gay Public Awareness Project, tells the story of Bobby Griffith
      10. "Naming Names": Lisa Graziano, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses the lesbian and gay civil rights bill.
      11. Clip of music video for "What's Up" by 4 Non Blondes.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 25 [Air date: 6/18/1993], June 1993; ID: 231.0146; 154379 (Box 10, Media ID: 231.0146)
      2. Footage of Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project event regarding opening a new office. Includes Lou Maletta interviewing Matt Foreman, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project. Also includes speech by Hon. Manfred Ohrenstein, NYS Senate Minority Leader.
      COMMERCIAL: "Re-elect Antonio Pagan [for] City Council". Includes footage from CSPAN of Antonio Pagan, of the NYC Council, speaking at the March on Washington.
      3. Footage of christening for new Hetrick-Martin Institute building at 2 Astor Place. Includes footage of Bill Hibsher, of the Board of Directors for the Hetrick-Martin Institute; Terrence McNally, playwright; Frances Kunreuther, Executive Director of the Hetrick-Martin Institute; and Jed Mattes, President of the Board of Directors for the Hetrick-Martin Institute.
      4. Footage of Stonewall Democrats awards dinner. Includes footage of [Eileen Mitzman], member of Mothers' Voices; Stockard Channing, actress; and Nick Curto, Founder of the Stonewall Business Association.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews [Dom DeCarlo], founder of gay fraternity, regarding his creation of Lambda Delta Phi.
      6. Paul Del Duca, Co-Chair of the Tristate Lesbian, Gay, & Bisexual Student Coalition, encourages students to get involved with a gay and lesbian student organization.
      7. Lou Maletta interviews Cynthia Marks and David Salvatore, of The CHARM Bracelet, regarding their charm bracelets AIDS fundraising effort.
      8. "Naming Names": Ellen Carton, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses recent bigoted NY Post cartoons.
      9. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Victoria C. Metaxas, Assistant Corporation Counsel for the NYC Law Department, and Irwin B. Kroot, Director of [Citywide Computer Training Program], regarding their organization "Coalition of Lesbian and Gay City Employees" in NYC.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 26 [Air date: 6/24/1993], June 1993; ID: 231.0147; 154380 (Box 10, Media ID: 231.0147)
      2. Footage of Mario Cuomo, NYS Governor, discussing lesbian and gay rights. Also includes Sheila Healy, Director of the Governor's Office for Lesbian and Gay Concerns, discussing Pride month.
      COMMERCIAL: 970 - BIG1
      3. Footage of mayor's reception for the gay and lesbian community. Includes footage of David Dinkins, NYC Mayor; Jay Hill, Executive Director of the Gay Games IV; Marty Rouse, Liaison for Manhattan Borough President; and Paula Ettelbrick, Executive Director of the Center for Lesbian Rights.
      4. Footage of Garden Party. Includes Kate Clinton, Mistress of Ceremonies. Also includes interviews with many attendees, including Cathay Che and Donald Suggs of GLAAD NY and Quentin Crisp.
      5. Interview: Joyce Hunter, President of the National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation, discusses lesbians and AIDS.
      6. [Helen and Anne], of the Lesbian Avengers, discuss the upcoming first annual Dyke March in Manhattan.
      7. Footage of the 2nd annual Pride Skate organized by the International Gay Skating Union (IGSU). Includes interviews with Laura Moore, organizer for IGSU, and Lisa Labrecque, figure skater.
      8. "Naming Names": Chiqui Cartagena, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent series from Entertainment TV (E TV) regarding gay and lesbian images in the media.
      COMMERCIAL: 970 – BIG1, Professional Male Models / Escorts Listing Service
      9. Interview: Ron Marx and Ed Rucinski, two Americans returning from Russia, discuss gay life and the recent lifting of the ban on gay male sex in Russia.
      COMMERCIAL: Cherry Grove Beach Club
      10. "Lavender Health": At the 3rd celebration of "Out in Government", Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Darryl Wong, from the Department of Mental Health, and Carl Day, of Human Resources Administration. Also includes Carrol Hunter discussing his personal life.
      11. Footage of Andy Humm [from 1992] interviewing Craig Rodwell, owner of Oscar Wilde Bookshop, regarding his gay and lesbian bookstore.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 27 [Air date: 7/1/1993], July 1993; ID: 231.0148; 154381 (Box 10, Media ID: 231.0148)
      2. Footage from Gay Pride 1993. Includes Ian Miller interviewing Randy Wicker, organizer of the Alternative [AIDS candlelight memorial] Vigil, and Brendan Fay, organizer of the Alternative [AIDS candlelight memorial] Vigil.
      COMMERCIAL: 970 – BIG1
      3. Footage of 12th annual [Front Runners Lesbian and Gay] Pride Run. Includes interviews with [Tony Meola], Race Director; Janet Weinberg, [activist]; Aaron Ashby, [who took] 3rd Place [in the] Community Challenge; Gerard King, male winner; and Stacy Creamer, female winner.
      4. Footage of the Lesbian Avengers Dyke March in Manhattan. Includes interviews with Marlene, Lesbian Avenger, and Katherine Acey, Executive Director of ASTRAEA.
      5. Footage of Gay Pride Rally 1993. Includes footage of Lea DeLaria, MC of rally, and Jimmy Somerville, singer.
      6. "Lavender Health": At the 3rd celebration of "Out in Government", Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Wayne Steinman, Founder of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns; Harold Robinson, founder of Gay Men of African Descent. Also includes speech by Captain Angela Kennedy, of the Department of Corrections.
      7. "Naming Names": Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses the recent NY Times article "Blacks Reject Gay Rights Fight as Equal to Theirs".
      8. Footage of gay pride parade. Includes footage of David Dinkins, NYC Mayor.
      9. Footage of Lesbian and Gay Pride fireworks and dance.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 27, Atlanta, GA, 1993; ID: 231.0149; 154382 (Box 10, Media ID: 231.0149)
      COMMERCIAL: "Why Not Love?"
      10. Clip of music video "Don't Talk Just Kiss" from Right Said Fred
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 28 [Air date: 7/8/1993], July 1993; ID: 231.0150; 154383 (Box 10, Media ID: 231.0150)
      2. Interview: Dick Dadey, of Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses the defeat of the NYS gay rights bill.
      3. Interview: Ellen Carton, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses the recent Newsday article "White Guys Can't Vote?" by Stephen Miller.
      4. Interview: Stephen Miller, gay media activist/writer, discusses his article "White Guys Can't Vote?".
      5. Lee Sharmat interviews Paula Ettelbrick, Director of Public Policy for the National Center for Lesbian Rights, regarding her new organization.
      6. Footage of Invasion of the Pines event.
      7. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King discusses the ban on gays in the military and the potential "Don't Ask, Don't Tell" policy.
      8. "Lavender Health": Ellen Zaltzberg, Deputy Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Joyce Hunter, of the HIV Center for Clinical and Behavioral Studies, regarding HIV news as well as the upcoming National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation Conference.
      9. "Naming Names": Michael Tancinco, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent Vanity Fair cover story about k.d. lang.
      10. Footage of benefit for the Campaign for Military Service. Includes Andy Humm interviewing Jerry Nadler, Democratic Congressman for Manhattan and Brooklyn; Tom Stoddard, of the Campaign for Military Service; Bill Rubenstein, of the ACLU Lesbian and Gay Rights Project; and Ernest Hopkins, of the Campaign for Military Service.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 29 [Air date: 7/15/1993], July 1993; ID: 231.0151; 154384 (Box 10, Media ID: 231.0151)